Allan M. Cormack Papers MS018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Allan M. Cormack Papers
1909 -- 1997
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Cormack, Allan MacLeod
MS018
12.85 Linear Feet 16 boxes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into eight series: Subject files; Notebooks; Correspondence; Meetings, ceremonies, lectures, and professional travel; Curricular material; Publications and presentations; Papers by other scientists; Photographs.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes papers documenting Allan M. Cormack's professional life, beginning with his early career at the University of Cape Town. The bulk of the material originates from Cormack's years as a professor of physics at Tufts. The material includes correspondence; notes and calculations; experimental data; reports, manuscripts, preprints, and reprints; lectures; course material; overhead transparencies; photographs; and video footage of a television interview with Cormack. These items relate to Cormack's scientific interests, including his research in particle and medical physics and applied mathematics, as well as other aspects of his physics career, such as pedagogical and administrative duties and peer and tenure review. Also recorded are Cormack's activities relating to the Nobel Prize and the Nobel Foundation.
Biographical / Historical
Allan MacLeod Cormack (1924-1998) joined Tufts in 1957 as a professor in the Department of Physics. A faculty member for 22 years, he received the Ballou Medal in 1978, and won the 1979 Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine for his work developing the computerized axial tomography (CAT) scan.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Faculty papers; Teaching and learning; Physics; Cormack, Allan MacLeod; Department of Physics and Astronomy
- Subject files, 1909 -- 1995; MS018.001; 5.1 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  Subject files kept by Allan MacLeod Cormack. The material documents Cormack's research in particle and medical physics and mathematics, in addition to other aspects of his professional life, including peer review for journals, colleagues' tenure review, and activities concerning the Nobel Prize and the Nobel Foundation. Most of the files are organized by scientific topics, with additional files categorized by names of individuals, organizations, and institutions and by titles of publications. The material includes research notes; experimental data; drafts, preprints, and reprints of papers; correspondence; overhead transparencies; and photographs.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Alpha and beta curves II, 1981 -- 1984; MS018.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - AAPM, 1988; MS018.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Absorption I, 1962 -- 1963; MS018.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Absorption II, 1964; MS018.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Ambartsumian--Eddington problem, 1966; MS018.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - App. magnetic guidance, 1989; MS018.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Archaeometry, 1970 -- 1972; MS018.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - British Journal of Radiology, 1975 -- 1976; MS018.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Brahme, 1992 -- 1994; MS018.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Brahme, Andres--Review of Brahme, "Optimization of Conformation and Generalized Moving Beam Radiation Therapy Techniques", 1987; MS018.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Brooks and DiChiro, 1971 -- 1976; MS018.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - C-CH2 Spectra/Energies, 1965 -- 1967; MS018.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Cell damage, 1972 -- 1974; MS018.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Circles tangential to circles (Globevnik), 1911; MS018.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Coalition for Reliable Engergy, 1988 -- 1991; MS018.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Cormack, "Diffraction by Atoms distributed at Random at Lattice Sites", 1954 -- 1962; MS018.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Cormack,"Some Distrubutions Associated with the Gompertz Mortality Law", 1990; MS018.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Cormack and Doyle, 1977 -- 1978; MS018.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Cormack, et al., "Elastic and scattering at 174 and 66 mev", 1958; MS018.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Data notes, correspondence, 1985; MS018.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Dead time losses, 1961; MS018.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Dosage in R3, 1983; MS018.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Dose distributions, 1979 -- 1994; MS018.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Dr. Masahiro Endo, 1977; MS018.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Field gradients, (1 of 3), MS018.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Field gradients, (2 of 3), MS018.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Field gradients, (3 of 3), 1982; MS018.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Grater manuscript, 1968; MS018.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Gabor Herman, 1977; MS018.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Gore and Leeman, 1978; MS018.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Gravitational imaging?, 1978; MS018.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Greitz, Nordenstrĕm, Soila, 1976 -- 1981; MS018.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Harvard Magazine, 1978; MS018.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Heat generated by neutrinos, 1956; MS018.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Helgason, Sigurdur, 1963 -- 1977; MS018.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Henrico Doctors' Hospital, Virginia, 1979 -- 1981; MS018.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Historic, 1980; MS018.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Hyp and Lemn in R(n), 1985; MS018.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Hyporgeom, Trauses, 1964 -- 1977; MS018.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Institute of Medicine, 1991 -- 1994; MS018.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Integrals over circles, 1979; MS018.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Integrative Psychiatry, 1983; MS018.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Inverse Problems, 1984 -- 1985; MS018.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Jaccard, C., 1980; MS018.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    Swiss Federal Institute for Snow and Avalanche Research
  - Jnsson, Dr. Leif, 1976; MS018.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Journal of Computer Assisted Tomography, 1976 -- 1980; MS018.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - K1=1/2, R^n: Radon's Problem, 1986 -- 1987; MS018.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Lewitt, R.M., 1977 -- 1978; MS018.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Lindau 87 Drawings, 1987; MS018.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Lindegaard - Anderson and Theusen, 1979; MS018.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - The Mathematics and Physics of Dose Radiation Planning Using X-Rays, 1989; MS018.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Massachusetts Citizens Against the Shutdown Initiative, 1988; MS018.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Measday, D.F. "Inelastics", 1967 -- 1975; MS018.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - MEDINFO and Coach Conferences, 1980; MS018.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Michaelies, Dr. Anthony R. "The Recovery of Science in Germany", 1981; MS018.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
    Interdisciplinary Science Reviews 6(4) 1981.
  - Miscellaneous mathematics, MS018.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous mathematics, Part 2, 1918 -- 1984; MS018.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous mathematics, Part 3, 1932 -- 1979; MS018.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Moliere, Gert, 1946; MS018.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Moran, J.P. and Brown, Randy, 1978 -- 1981; MS018.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
    Contains Cormack's beat-down of Moran ("Moron")and Brown's ("Brawn's") attempt to dispute his Hole Theorem
  - The Effects of Multiple Scattering in Small-Angle Nuclear Scattering Experiments, 1961; MS018.001.002.00020; Cormack, Allan MacLeod (Box 2)
  - Draft of "The Effects of Multiple...", 1961; MS018.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Draft of "The Effects of Multiple...", 1961; MS018.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - N-total neutron cross sections, 1956 -- 1967; MS018.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Nature electrostatics, 1979 -- 1986; MS018.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Neutron beam, MS018.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - NMR imaging in medicine - overhead transparencies, MS018.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - NMR zeugmatography, 1975 -- 1982; MS018.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Nobel Foundation, 1988 -- 1989; MS018.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Nobel lecture, 1979 -- 1980; MS018.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Norton, Stephen, 1979 -- 1994; MS018.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Note on algorithms, 1979; MS018.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Nuclear energy, 1988; MS018.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - New York Times letter, 1993; MS018.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - P-N, 1965; MS018.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Papiez, Lech - preprints, 1995; MS018.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Parabaloids cardioids in Rn, 1984 -- 1987; MS018.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
    handwritten
  - Perry, R.M. "Reconstructing a Function by Circular Harmonic Analysis of the Radon Transform", 1975; MS018.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Photon doses, MS018.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
    handwritten.
  - Physics Bulletin letter, 1977; MS018.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Physics Today, 1979 -- 1980; MS018.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Plasmas Sauthoff, 1978 -- 1980; MS018.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - Preziosi and Capece, 1979; MS018.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Projections correspondence, 1971 -- 1972; MS018.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - Proton radiography, MS018.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - Protons, 1973 -- 1975; MS018.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
    mainly from Koehler, A.M.
  - Quantitative proton tomography, 1976; MS018.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - Quinto, Doyle, 1979 -- 1980; MS018.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - R^2 x = 1/m Closed Foam, MS018.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
  - R Hyp + Lmn in R^2, 1980; MS018.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
  - Parabaloids and cardioids, MS018.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Rad. Med. Vis. Com (1 of 2), 1995; MS018.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Rad. Med. Vis. Com (2 of 2), 1995; MS018.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Radiotherapy non-negativity, 1950 -- 1986; MS018.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Radon, r cos (alpha)(theta)=p, 1981; MS018.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Radon r cos (alpha)(theta)=p, Cormack, MS018.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Random lattice cites, 1963; MS018.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Reconstruction radon, 1972 -- 1976; MS018.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Referee reports, 1973 -- 1974; MS018.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Reprints and reference material, related to problems in X-ray Imaging, 1982; MS018.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Reprints and reference material, related to problems in X-ray Imaging, Kjellberg and Kliman, cost of treatment, 1982; MS018.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Reprints, by Cormack and others, and notes, (1 of 2), 1959 -- 1968; MS018.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Reprints, by Cormack and others, and notes, (1 of 2), 1959 -- 1968; MS018.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Reprints, by Cormack and others, and notes, HIlberg and Rothe, 1957 -- 1971; MS018.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Reprints, correspondence, and notes, 1980 -- 1995; MS018.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Reprints, notes, 1972 -- 1983; MS018.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Research notes, 1968 -- 1969; MS018.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Reviews, 1974 -- 1978; MS018.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Rot. ther. III, 1989; MS018.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Rotation expansions, 1988; MS018.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Rotation therapy, 1980 -- 1987; MS018.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Rotation therapy II, 1986; MS018.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Rotation therapy III, 1989; MS018.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Rouland Foundation, 1978 -- 1980; MS018.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Royal Society of South Africa, 1983; MS018.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Russell Mills, 1977; MS018.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Sampling and emission scanners, 1979; MS018.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - Sampling the radon transform, 1976; MS018.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Scanning, 1957 -- 1961; MS018.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Scatter raiography, 1973 -- 1975; MS018.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Schotland, 1983 -- 1994; MS018.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Science at the Bicentennial, National Science Board, 1976; MS018.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Sigmund, multiple scattering, 1975; MS018.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - Single County, 1964; MS018.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - Slocum, John T., 1977; MS018.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Small angle negative polarizations, 1959 -- 1965; MS018.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - SPIE Article, 1990; MS018.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Stable solutions and sums, 1983; MS018.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Stanford Pion Beam, 1971 -- 1973; MS018.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Stopping Koano, Special Theory, 1964 -- 1975; MS018.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Ssskind, 1980; MS018.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Sznajd, Dr. Graznya, 1991 -- 1993; MS018.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Toshiba Medical Review, 1980 -- 1987; MS018.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - University of British Columbia, 1980; MS018.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Uhlenback and statistical mechanics..., 1909 -- 1989; MS018.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Uniform n-Dimension external transform, 1979; MS018.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Steward, V.W., 1973 -- 1978; MS018.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Vavilov, 1957 -- 1968; MS018.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Weekly Shonen Jump Article, 1992 -- 1994; MS018.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Widgoff, 1965; MS018.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Widgoff, 1970 -- 1971; MS018.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Z-D Reconstructing History, 1963 -- 1978; MS018.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Publications, 1952; MS018.001.006.00001 (Box MS018 Shared 1)
  - Bacteriophage, MS018.001.006.00002 (Box MS018 Shared 1)
  - "Mssbauer Effect and the Phase Problem in X-ray Crystallography", 1962; MS018.001.006.00003 (Box MS018 Shared 1)
  - Bacteriophages, 1950; MS018.001.006.00004 (Box MS018 Shared 1)
  - Timing Relations, Diffusion, and the Mssbauer Effect, 1966; MS018.001.006.00005 (Box MS018 Shared 1)
  - Diffusion and bacteriophages, MS018.001.006.00006 (Box MS018 Shared 1)
  - Absorption, old letters, letters from Titchmarsh, Sears, Run o data reduction, 1959; MS018.001.006.00007 (Box MS018 Shared 1)
- Notebooks, 1952 -- 1978; MS018.002; 1.7 Linear Feet
  This series contains Cormack's notebooks. Looseleaf notes removed from binders, as well as a few bound notebooks. Cormack labeled most of the binders and notebooks by subject. The material originates from Cormack's time at the University of Cape Town through his years on the Tufts faculty. It includes research notes and calculations, drafts of papers for publication, experimental data, reprints, correspondence, and X-ray images of archaeological and fine arts objects.
  Included in this material are notes, data, and drafts used to prepare the 1963 and 1964 radiological papers for which Cormack was awarded the Nobel Prize.
  - Untitled notebook, research notes and data, University of Cape Town, MS018.002.006.00008 (Box MS018 Shared 1)
  - Untitled notebook, tutorials, absorption data, University of Cape Town, MS018.002.006.00009 (Box MS018 Shared 1)
  - Absorption I databook, 1962 -- 1964; MS018.002.006.00010 (Box MS018 Shared 1)
  - Absorption II databook, 1964; MS018.002.006.00011 (Box MS018 Shared 1)
  - Absorption I, MS018.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Absorption data, MS018.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Chemical effects, 1968; MS018.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Multiple scattering I, 1952; MS018.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Multiple scattering II, 1962; MS018.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Multiple scattering III, 1960; MS018.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Proton Tomography, Jan-June, 1975; MS018.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Proton Tomography, 1975; MS018.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Proton Tomography, 1901 -- 1976; MS018.002.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Proton Tomography, February 4-August, 1976; MS018.002.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Radon calculations, 1972; MS018.002.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Untitled notebook, mathematical notes, particle physics, MS018.002.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Untitled notebook, radon transform, MS018.002.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Untitled notebook, radon transform, 1978; MS018.002.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Untitled notebook, radon transform, test of July 1963 data, MS018.002.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Untitled notebook, X-ray images, 1977; MS018.002.007.00016 (Box 7)
- Correspondence, 1979 -- 1994; MS018.003; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series includes correspondence received and sent by Cormack, organized by last name of correspondent (including individuals, organizations, and institutions). Most of the correspondence was exchanged with colleagues about research matters, although non-professional correspondence is included as well. The files also contain a number of reprints.
  - A, 1989; MS018.003.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - B, 1980 -- 1988; MS018.003.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - C, 1984 -- 1993; MS018.003.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - D, 1985; MS018.003.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - E, 1982; MS018.003.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - F, 1982 -- 1990; MS018.003.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - G, 1982 -- 1985; MS018.003.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - H, 1980 -- 1989; MS018.003.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - I, 1988; MS018.003.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - J, MS018.003.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - K, 1982 -- 1989; MS018.003.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - L, 1982 -- 1988; MS018.003.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - M, 1983 -- 1987; MS018.003.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - N, 1986; MS018.003.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - P, 1979 -- 1988; MS018.003.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Q, 1984 -- 1985; MS018.003.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - R, 1981 -- 1982; MS018.003.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - S, 1983 -- 1994; MS018.003.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - T, 1985; MS018.003.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - V, 1980 -- 1990; MS018.003.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - W, 1982 -- 1991; MS018.003.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - Z, 1984 -- 1985; MS018.003.008.00022 (Box 8)
- Meetings, ceremonies, lectures, and professional travel, 1974 -- 1997; MS018.004; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains material relating to conferences, invited lectures, award ceremonies, interviews, and other professional events and travel. Cormack arranged the files chronologically by event or destination. The material includes correspondence, notes for lectures delivered, conference programs and proceedings, papers discussed, and overhead transparencies for presentations. Documentation of travel expenses has been discarded. Among the events documented are meetings and ceremonies for Nobel Prize winners.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Brookhaven, (1 of 2), 1974; MS018.004.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Brookhaven, (2 of 2), 1974; MS018.004.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - San Juan, 1976; MS018.004.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Bethesda, 1976; MS018.004.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Oberwolfach, 1980; MS018.004.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Mocton, 1976 -- 1980; MS018.004.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Museum of Science and Industry, Chicago, 1979 -- 1980; MS018.004.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - American Physical Society, Washington, 1979 -- 1980; MS018.004.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Tokyo, 1980; MS018.004.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Tokyo, 1980; MS018.004.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Argonne-Kramer, 1980; MS018.004.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Long Beach, 1979 -- 1980; MS018.004.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Cleveland Clinic, 1980; MS018.004.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Alberta, September, 1981; MS018.004.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Chile, August 5-9, 1981; MS018.004.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - American Medical International, Long Island, June 12-19, 1981; MS018.004.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Dallas, 1981; MS018.004.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Westchester Co. Medical Society, 1981; MS018.004.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Tokyo, Dr. Takayoshi Matsui, 1981; MS018.004.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Massachusetts Maritime Academy, 1981; MS018.004.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - U Mass-Amherst, 1981; MS018.004.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Philip Morris, October 29 and 30, 1981; MS018.004.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Health and Human Services, Washington, November 4-6, 1981; MS018.004.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - M. D. Anderson, Houston, November 11-13, 1981; MS018.004.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - International Symposium on Stress, 1981; MS018.004.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Washington University, 1982; MS018.004.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - American Medical Society, January 11-12, 1982; MS018.004.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - University of California-Irvine, March 14-16, 1982; MS018.004.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Trieste, March 30-April 2, 1982; MS018.004.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - Trois Riviere, April 21-23, 1982; MS018.004.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Korea, May 5-8, 1982; MS018.004.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - University of Pennsylvania, September 22, 1982; MS018.004.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - SUNY New Paltz, 1982; MS018.004.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - Palm Springs, 1982; MS018.004.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - George Washington University Medical Center, October 30-November 2, 1982; MS018.004.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - Japan, 1983; MS018.004.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - Japan, 1983; MS018.004.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - KTP Trieste, Medical Physics, 1983; MS018.004.009.00039 (Box 9)
  - Santa Barbara, 1983; MS018.004.009.00040 (Box 9)
  - American Mathematical Society, April 12-13, 1983; MS018.004.009.00041 (Box 9)
  - Medic, Canada, May 19-31, 1983; MS018.004.009.00042 (Box 9)
  - Washington DC, June 15-16, 1983; MS018.004.009.00043 (Box 9)
  - Massachusetts Eye and Ear Infirmary, 1983; MS018.004.009.00044 (Box 9)
  - Kodak, 1982; MS018.004.009.00045 (Box 9)
  - APS, Burlington, Vermont, 1983; MS018.004.009.00046 (Box 9)
  - Sorbonne - FNAC 26-29 Oct., 1983; MS018.004.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Trieste, 1983; MS018.004.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Cath U D.C., 1984; MS018.004.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - N.R.L. Wash, 1984; MS018.004.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - U. of Dallas, 1984; MS018.004.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - S.P.S.E. Lexington, 1984; MS018.004.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - A.P.A. Los Angeles, 1984; MS018.004.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - AAAS New York, 1984; MS018.004.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Lindau June 25-29, 1984; MS018.004.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Manitoba 13-14 Aug, 1984; MS018.004.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Talloires, 1984; MS018.004.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - U.C. Davis, 1985; MS018.004.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Brooklyn Poly, 1985; MS018.004.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - Max Entropy - Colo. Aug 5-8, 1985; MS018.004.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Joint Center Oct 18 9am, 1985; MS018.004.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - Cen Conn State, 1985; MS018.004.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - Schlumberger, 1985; MS018.004.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - New Orleans Jan 7-12 AMS, 1986; MS018.004.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - Loichita State Mar 16-18, 1986; MS018.004.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - Irvine April 2-4, 1986; MS018.004.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - R.P.I., 1986; MS018.004.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - Wash D.C., 1986; MS018.004.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - Max. Ent. Seattle 5-8 Aug, 1986; MS018.004.010.00023 (Box 10)
  - Nat. Lib. Medicine, 1986; MS018.004.010.00024 (Box 10)
  - Nobel Dinner, 1986; MS018.004.010.00025 (Box 10)
  - U. Lowell, 1987; MS018.004.010.00026 (Box 10)
  - U. Mass Worcester, 1987; MS018.004.010.00027 (Box 10)
  - Lindau June 29-31, 1987; MS018.004.010.00028 (Box 10)
  - Giessen GJL, 1987; MS018.004.010.00029 (Box 10)
  - Bos. Leadership Forum, 1987; MS018.004.010.00030 (Box 10)
  - U. of Toronto, 1988; MS018.004.010.00031 (Box 10)
  - Berlin Jan 15-16, 1988; MS018.004.010.00032 (Box 10)
  - Japan Mar 6-12, 1988; MS018.004.010.00033 (Box 10)
  - Dayton, 1988; MS018.004.010.00034 (Box 10)
  - Eur Soc Cardiol Aug 28-Sep 1, 1988; MS018.004.010.00035 (Box 10)
  - T-V Production, 1988; MS018.004.010.00036 (Box 10)
  - Lubbock TX Nov 4-5, 1988; MS018.004.010.00037 (Box 10)
  - Ft. Lauderdale, 1989; MS018.004.010.00038 (Box 10)
  - Harvard Cyclotron, 1989; MS018.004.010.00039 (Box 10)
  - Hosp of U Penn, 1989; MS018.004.010.00040 (Box 10)
  - Neurosurgery MGH, 1989; MS018.004.010.00041 (Box 10)
  - Long Beach, 1989; MS018.004.010.00042 (Box 10)
  - A.M.S. Arcata June 24-30, 1989; MS018.004.010.00043 (Box 10)
  - Mayo Clinic, 1989; MS018.004.010.00044 (Box 10)
  - Bockwinkel Uhlenbeck Grunbaum, 1989; MS018.004.010.00045 (Box 10)
  - O.N.R., 1989; MS018.004.010.00046 (Box 10)
  - AAAS New Orleans 15-20 Feb, 1990; MS018.004.010.00047 (Box 10)
  - Lindau, 1990; MS018.004.010.00048 (Box 10)
  - Milano, 1990; MS018.004.010.00049 (Box 10)
  - Stockholm, 1991; MS018.004.010.00050 (Box 10)
  - Radon - Vienna Aug/Sep, 1992; MS018.004.010.00051 (Box 10)
  - Columbus Bos., 1992; MS018.004.010.00052 (Box 10)
  - Japan, 1992; MS018.004.010.00053 (Box 10)
  - Boston Coll, 1992; MS018.004.010.00054 (Box 10)
  - Keules, 1993; MS018.004.010.00055 (Box 10)
  - Lindau, 1993; MS018.004.010.00056 (Box 10)
  - South Biomed Eng Conf, 1994; MS018.004.010.00057 (Box 10)
  - AAAS Gingerich Tues, 1995; MS018.004.010.00058 (Box 10)
  - U.S. C.G.A., 1995; MS018.004.010.00059 (Box 10)
  - Cape Town, 1995; MS018.004.010.00060 (Box 10)
  - Korea, 1995; MS018.004.010.00061 (Box 10)
  - New York, 1995; MS018.004.010.00062 (Box 10)